

KAYLA DATTE

PHONE: 858.382.8313 EMAIL: KAYLADATTE@GMAIL.COM

OBJECTIVE

I am an experienced Office Manager with a strong background in customer service and administrative work who is looking for a new challenge. At my current company I rose from Administrative Assistant to Office Manager within one year and have held the position for over four years.

SKILLS

Organizational, Written and Verbal Communication, Data Entry, Excel, Attention to Detail, Microsoft Office Suite, Problem Solving, Scheduling, Time Management, Conflict Resolution, Office Management, Training, Management

EXPERIENCE

OFFICE MANAGER • NEXTACE • 07/2016 - PRESENT

Assist CEO directly regarding scheduling and other various tasks assigned

Track and update registrations and memberships with Trade Associations for CEO

Coordinate travel arrangements for all staff members including booking flights, hotel stays and rental cars. Manage itineraries of employees before and during travel, including last-minute changes

Organize and oversee company community outreach events and projects

Prepare, finalize and submit expense reports for CEO and top-level management using iExpense in Oracle

Gather and submit Invoices to Accounting

Log and deposit payments from Vendors

Act as liaison regarding major facilities needs

Coordinate all office upgrades/updates

Coordinate monthly Staff and Management meeting

Oversee/complete set up, food and visuals for meetings

Manage job postings: Indeed, ZipRecruiter, Taleo, any others as needed

Coordinate team building and company morale events

Set up interviews and obtain applications from prospective job applicants

Liaison between corporate HR and NextAce staff

Maintain Vacation Calendar

Follow up with Time Off Requests

Other miscellaneous tasks as assigned

OFFICE MANAGER • RICHARD C. FREY FINE ARTS & APPRAISALS • 2015-2016

Managed daily office operations including customer service and incoming clients.









KAYLA DATTE

Handled sales of artwork and antiques on a variety of sales websites including eBay, Etsy, the company website etc. In charge of appraisal layouts and price research. Processed payroll and managed the business and personal financial accounts of the owner as well as paying bills. Input all finances, customers and vendors into QuickBooks and balanced accounts.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN SOCIOLOGY • 2014 • ARIZONA STATE UNIVERSITY

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Association for Supportive Child Care

Oct 2014 - Dec 2014

Provided life development advice for both children and adolescents from ages 5-18.

Helped students from K-12 to understand and complete homework assignments.

Provided emotional support for a multitude of people.

Community Service Programs (CSP, Inc)

Feb 2017 - Nov 2017

Provide emotional support for survivors of sexual assaults via hotline and support for hospital exam.